Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Audiotapes
  - General Personalities, Jerry Lewis on Jack Paars Show, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_324; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Genoveva (Schumann)- Il Ritorno (Mendellsohn), 02/08/1962; 02/09/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_354; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Gershwin Memorial - Bing Crosby (Film Shorts) Alexanders Ragtime Band (Alice Faye) Symphony No. 2 (Furtwangler), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_459; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Gilda - Thief and The Hangman - Edmond Clement - J.J. Niles - J. Ray- Feathertop - Aksel Schiotz - Blossom Seely, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_292; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Gioconda (Cerqueti) Rheingold (Flagstad) Arlesienn (BBC) - Kraft Music Hall (Crosby) It's In the Bag Rube Bloom - Waller, 10/15/1942; 10/22/1942; 10/29/1942; bell_brothers_tapes_611; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Gioconda, Gen. Patton; Iceland, S. Heine; Sandhog, Earl Robinson, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_497; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Gladys Swarthout - Cornelia O. Skinner - Chapman, Bar. Otello Metropolitan Cooper - M. Makeba, 03/23/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_583; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Glen Miller and Tommy Dorsey broadcasts, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_001; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Glenn Miller and Benny Goodman broadcasts, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_003; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Go Into Your dance (Jolson) Mammy Singing Fool (Jolson) - Rose Washington Square (Jolson) Flying Down to Rio (G. Rogers), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_322; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Going Hollywood - Toscanini - J. Marsala; D. Reinhardt - Vivaldi; Duke Ellington; C. Larry Adler - Anssea Ten, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_585; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Golden Earrings, (Excerpt - Marlene Dietrich): Give us this Nigth; It's a great Life, Shostakovich; So this is Love, (Concluded), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_539; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Gotterdammerung (Convent Garden); Hulda (Franck) - EineFiorentinische Tragodie (Zemlinsky) - Clarion Concert - WNYC, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_368; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Gotterdammerung - Bayreuth Festival - (Part 1), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_127; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Gotterdammerung - Bayreuth Festival - (Part 2), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_128; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Gracie Fields; S. Holloway; Burl Ives; Renata Tebaldo; Chavales de Espana - TV; Stefan Wolpe, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_240; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Grasshopper; Oliver Twist; Oregon Paper Strike; Tratini; Bach; Biber; Geminiani; G. B. Show; Hello Frisco Hello; Orfeo, Gluck; Jan Hanish, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_549; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - H. Lashanska; Summer Stock; Xmas Holiday; Do you love me; Wake up Dream, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_495; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - H. S. Truman, Day Earth Stood Still, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_496; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Hallelujah Im a bum, Jolson; Say it with songs, Al Jolson; Jussi Bjoerling, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_323; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Hamlet, (four and a half hours); Music for strings Dinu Lipatti, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_627; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Happy Go Lucky; Litany to the Virgin Maryby, Szmanowski; Mildred Bailey; Frank Sinatra; Ginevra; Delannoy; Rhapsody in Blue, George Jessel; Alex Schiotz; Vaudeville Comedy, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_420; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Happy Landing - Coronado -Underpup -Something for the Boys - Golden Voices, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_365; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Hark The Years, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_071; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Harold Rome - Tony Bennett - Como - La Guardia - Hindemith, Etc.; D. martin - M. Berle, 03/07/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_363; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Harry Belafonte TV, 12/10/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_007; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Harry Belafonte, TV, 11/20/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_116; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Harry S Truman Le Campane Romance Guardia Civil - Alleluia #2 Johnny Holiday, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_265; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Hedda Hopper Review. A Decade in Review, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_435; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Hercules; Mighty Joe Young; Edison; W. Willkie; K. Rockne; Seagull, C. Hull; Forza del Destino, Film, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_557; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Here Come the Waves; Peter Pan, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_206; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - High, Wide, and Handsome Film; Irene Dunne, Dorothy Lamour, undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_015 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Histoire Du Solfat (Stravinsky Berwald - Kath. Long) Le Rossignol (Stravinsky) Polish Jazz Combo; Oboe Trio (Roman) A. Rubinstein - Hollywood Canteen Seven Keys to Baldpate (Cohan), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_455; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Hit Parade - H. Hoover - Hugo Wolf Songs - 20th Century - Masked Ball - 3 Musketeers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_257; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Hit Parade, Conchita Supervia, Film, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_203; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Hollywood Canteen B. Russell - George VI - Iris (Mascagni) - Legend of Ohrid (Hristic) - Living Death (M. Atkinson) Queen Elizabeth II - King David (Honegger), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_456; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Hootenanny; Flying Dutchman - L. Tibett - Don Quixote Chaliapin - O. Kline; Leon Rothier - Lady from the Sea (Ibsen) R. Donat, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_663; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Hootenanny Folk Music (#1) - Four Jills and a Jeep - Toscanini - Bell Telephone Hour - Nilsson - As Long as They're Happy Jack Buchanan, 04/11/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_599; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Huguenots; La Juive, Pablo Casals; Carl Nielsen; Jazz Pastor, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_298; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Hunyadi Laszlo (Erkel) - Drei Pintos (Weber) Stravinsky - Don Procopio (Bizet) Bela Bartok - Sullivan, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_616; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Hypatia, Caitani; Beatrice and Benedict, Berlioz; Elisir DAmore, Donizetti; Symphony No. 3, Mahler, 05/12/1962; 04/17/1960; 02/05/1949; bell_brothers_tapes_439; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - I Married an Angel, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_098; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - I Virtuosi Ambulanti, Fioravanti; Capitan Bruno, Wissmer; Astuzzi Feminili, Cimarosa, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_523; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - I. Berlin, J. Roll Morton; Psalms, Ellington, Wacs; Joselito, F. Wright, Eichmaann, Hit the Ice, W. S. Mervin; Bath Festival; Beatrice Kay, Kennedy, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_331; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Idomeno (Mozart) - Luci Metropolitan (Sutherland), 12/09/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_340; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Il Duca D'Alba (Donizetti) Kirsten Flagstad (Miscellaneous), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_665; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Il Progionero (Dallapiccola); Lo Speziale (Haydn), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_168; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Il re de Dolore (Caldara) - Cantor Barkin - Sir John; In Love (Vaughan Williams) - Miscellaneous Haydn, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_358; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Il Travatore, Verdi, Metropolitan, (Part 1), 03/13/1943; bell_brothers_tapes_171; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box box 13)
  - Il Travatore, Verdi, Metropolitan, (Part 2), 03/13/1943; bell_brothers_tapes_172; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Il Vorfice (Rossellini) Kingdom (Elgar) Lincantesimo (Montemezz I) La Donna E Mobile - (Malipiero) - Bertrand Russell, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_319; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - I'll see you in my dreams; Francesca Da Rimini, Zandonai; Top Hat; Wintertime; Victorian Musical Box, Ed Clement, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_300; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - I'm no Angel, Mae West; Doctor Rhythm, Crosby; She loves me not, Crosby; C. Darrow; Minstrel Show; Pope John XXIII, Vaudeville, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_527; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - In Old Chicago; Aniara, Blomdahl, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_144; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Indifferent Lover; No Exit, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_231; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Indonesia Maria Kurenko - For Me and My Gal - Dido and Aeneas - (Purcell)) - Alb. Berg, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_267; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Infidelita Delusa (Haydn)- Daphne (R. Straus); Ivan Terrible (Rimsky-Korsakoff) Sonata 2 Pianos - Cancer Var. - Gleason; Sinatra; etc., 1958; bell_brothers_tapes_355; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Ingrid Bergman 24 Hours in a Womans Life, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_052; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Intermezzo (R. Strauss); Miracle Doctor, Bizet; Works by Stoessel USO Story, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_307; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Invisible City of Kitezh (Rimsky - Korsakoff) Bolshoi, undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_050 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Iphigenia EuEulide, Glcuck; Dmitri, Dvorak; Symphony No. 2, Walton, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_303; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Irma La Douce; Make me an offer, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_087; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Irmgard Seefried, Missa Solemnis, Pro Face, Casella; C. B. Shaw Crticisms; Patti; Butt; Joachim; Sarasate; Ysaye, etc.; Perry Como; Harold Rome, 03/28/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_437; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Isabeau Mascagni Fedora Giordano Radio: Jolson and Grey Radio Concert (Tagliavini, etc.), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_377; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Italian in Algiers; I Due Foscari; Ana Bolena; Maria Callas, Rehearsal, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_447; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Ives Montand - Danny Kaye - Crosby - Green, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_279; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - J. Andrews and Carol Burnett In C. Hall - College Holiday Burning Bright Schoenberg and Stravinsky - Tito Schipa, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_462; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - J. Dos Passos - War Requiem (Britten) Hootenanny Prades Festival (Casals) - Voice of Firestone; Carnegie Hall (Jazz) (Developments of New Jazz); Louis Armstrong - Mayor G. Christopher, 06/15/1963; 06/16/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_600; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Jason Robards, Jr. - Robert and Gaby Casadesus Barrymore - F. Chadwick - Hubbard Hanus - Suchon - Carl Nielsen - Israel in Egypt (Handel), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_593; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Jerry Lewis - Tonight Shows, 07/02/1962; 07/03/1962; 07/04/1962; 07/05/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_477; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Jerry Lewis - TV - Perry Como; Flanders and Swann - TV - Lagrime D Amante; Al Sepolcro Dell Amata (Monteverdi) Ziegfeld Girl (Concluded), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_429; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Jerry Lewis: (On Tonight Show), 06/25/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_464; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Jerry Lewis; Bertrand Russell, 11/19/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_466; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Joan Sutherland; Bernardo De muro; Arthur Schwartz; It happened in Brooklyn ], Sinatra; Baroness Von Trapp, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_349; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - John Browns Body (Benet) - Dracula (Orson Wells) Town Crier (Alex Woolcott), 1938; 10/06/1933; bell_brothers_tapes_657; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - John F. Kennedy, Nomination speech, 07/15/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_112; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - John McCormack; W. Churchill; Piano Concerto, Dvorak; S. Richter, Miscellaneous Personalities, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_476; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Johnny Johnson (Weill), 03/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_275; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Jolson Story; Duffy's Tavern, The Trails of Ch. De Gaulle; Lost Horizon; Venus and Adonis, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_178; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Jongleur Notre Dam, Massenet; Djamileh Bzet; Feutrsnot, R. Strauss; Emilia Di Liverpool; Donizetti; Robin Hood; Tribute to Bob Hope, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_302; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Joyce Grenfell - Richter - Red Buttons - Paderewski - Ferrier - valentino - Mrs. Kennedy - Valentino, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_268; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Joyce Grenfell, Oliver, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_086; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - K. Smith; D. Durbin; Marna Loy; Perry Como; F. D. R., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_530; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Kamakawa - Bloch - Bandings - Arrieu Damase - Bach - Vivaldi - Bernac - Mendelssohn - Battistini - Three Little Girls in Blue, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_489; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Katya Kabanova (Leos Janacek), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_190; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Katya Kabanova (Leos Janacek), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_191; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Kennedy - Nixon Debates: 1st and 2nd, 09/26/1960; 10/07/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_113; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Kennedy speeches, assassination, interviews with political figures, 11/22/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_676; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Kennedys European Trip - The Dragon (Play); CBC/BBC Special Program - Don Quichotte (Courbois) Ethel Waters: Paul Robeson, 07/06/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_613; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Kim Borg, Etc., Rachmaninoff, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_383; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - King David, Honegger, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_467; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - King Kong; Son of Kong; Adriana Lecouvreur; Cilea; Kirsten Flagstad; Helen Mack-Yoga, 02/09/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_548; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Kingston Trio; Perry Como; Yanki, No., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_065; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - L. Bernstein; Hers To Hold, N. Eddy; Meistersinger, Joan Sutherland; Meet the People, M. Chevalier; Carlo Galeffi, Bell Telefhone Hour, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_708; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - L. Bernstein; Hers To Hold, N. Eddy; Meistersinger, Joan Sutherland; Meet the People, M. Chevalier; Carlo Galeffi, Bell Telefhone Hour, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_709; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - La Boheme, Sayao; De Luca; Pinza; A. Dickey, etc.; Elizabeth Rethberg, (Early recording), 02/10/1940; bell_brothers_tapes_630; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - La Cenerentola, Rossini; Tom Dooley; Romeo and Juliet, TV; Andrea Chenier, Met; Mary Garden, 03/02/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_554; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - La Clementina, Symphony No. 57, Haydn; Sonata, Szymanowsky; Missa Sancta, John McCormack, Dawes, Corregidor; She's Working her way Thru College, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_473; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - La Dame Blanche (Boildieu) - Roberta Song of Norway- Johnny Johnson and Der Jasager (Kurt Weill) Gurre - Lieder - (Schoenberg), 08/10/1937; 08/17/1937; 08/24/1937; 08/31/1937; 10/13/1937; 10/16/1937; 10/20/1937; 10/21/1937; 10/30/1937; 11/04/1937; 11/06/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_614; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - La Dona Del Lago, Rossini; Nerone, Boito, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_622; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - La Fida Niifa; Schipa; Del Monaco; Pola Negri; F. D. R.; Scientists; Donizetti; Claudi Muzio, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_537; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - La Gioconda (Ponchielli) (Part 1), undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_016 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - La Gioconda (Ponchielli) (Part 2), undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_017 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - La Perichole, Metropolitan Opera Company, 02/10/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_350; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - La Perichole, Offenbach, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_145; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Ladies Man; Hitler; Aleko, Rachmaninoff; Mireille, Gounod, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_413; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Lady be Good - Lucia (Sutherland) - M. Rostropovitch - Une Education Man quee (Chabrier) - Jolson, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_697; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Lady be Good - Lucia (Sutherland) - M. Rostropovitch - Une Education Man quee (Chabrier) - Jolson, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_698; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Lady Be Good; Cover Girl, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_082; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Lady in the Dark - Mass in D Minor (Dvorak) - Nehru- Rose Marie Bitter Sweet - M. Martin and D. Powel - Ghost Catchers - Music of the Thirties, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_294; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Lakme, Lily Pons, E. Pinza, Metropolitan Opera Broadcast, 01/06/1940; bell_brothers_tapes_068; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - L'Amfiparnaso, Vecchi, Film; Nineteen eighty four, Orwell; You were never Lovelier, Film;; Adriana; Lecouvreur; Busoni; Morell; Albrechtsberger; Danzi; Roger Marton; Der Gross inquisitor, Boris Blacher, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_502; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - L'Amour Jaloux; Les Fetes D'Hebe; Castor et Pollux; Rene Saint-Aude Orch., Haitian Music; Player Pianos, Nineteen hundred; L. Goldowsky; Morath, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_531; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Le Donne Curiose (Wolf - Ferrari)- Fierrabras (Schubert) - Adrast (Schubert), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_262; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Le Jolie Fille De Perth (Bizet) - Paris and Helen (Gluck) Koenigskinder (Humperdinck), 04/18/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_399; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Le Maschere Beethoven - Ives Bartok, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_490; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Legends, Sibelius; Men and Mountains Ruggles; P. Pears; Symphony No. 3, Becker; Music for Orch., Riegger; Cantata, Bach; The Deum, Barraud; Don Juan, Liszt; Concerto for Violin and Orch., Bloch; Coups De Roulis, Messenger; Ma Tante, Boildieu; Hearts Assurance, Tippett; Une Educatione Manquee, Chabrier, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_516; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Lehar - Merry Widow; Jeanette Macdonald; Maurice Chevalier, 05/10/1934; "bell_brothers_tapes_046 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Leremo, Constantini; Danton Tod, Von Einem, Bach; V. Williams; Elgar; Bayes; O. Wells; Shostakovich; Copland; Coolidge; Beethoven; Norworth, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_569; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Let Freedom Ring (Nelson Eddy) #2, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_097; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Let Freedom Ring Nelson Eddy, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_096; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - L'Etoile; Brass quartet; Padmavati, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_551; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Life Begins at 40 (Will Rogers), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_211; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Life of Carlos Gardel, Film, Coriolanus BBC; Krutnava, Suchon, Lotte Lehmanns Farewell concert, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_119; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Life of the Party (Joe Penner), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_218; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Lili Lehmann - Selma Kurz - Margarette Siems - Louise Kirby - Lunn - Lotte Lehmann, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_452; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Lincoronazione Di Poppea (Monteverdi) Firestone; Fille Jolie De Perth (Bizet) - Toscanini- J.V. Cunningham, 03/24/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_400; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Linda Di Chamounix, Donzti; Annie get your gun, Garland; Opera Singers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_491; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Little Princess Ramona - Telethon, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_338; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Live and Let live Mel Powell and Babbitt - Helge Roswaenge - Malvena (Hahn) - H.L. Mencken- Jimmy Doolittle - Bori - Belhomme- Isobell Baillie, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_486; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Lo Schiavo; Lolanthe; Griseldis; Le Petite Sireuse, 04/02/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_177; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Lohengrin Metropolitan Opera (Part 1), 01/02/1943; bell_brothers_tapes_184; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Lohengrin Metropolitan Opera (Part 2), 01/02/1943; bell_brothers_tapes_185; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Lohengrin Texaco-Metropolitan Opera; Radio Network, 02/01/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_683; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Lohengrin, Flagstad; Bransell; Mason, Metropolitan Opera, (Part 2), 03/27/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_070; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Lohengrin, Flagstad, Metropolitan Opera, (Part 1), 03/27/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_069; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Louis Armstrong - All - Star Jazz, TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_032; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Louis Armstrong, The Brute, Moss; Eugen Onegin Film; Gigli, Lauri, Volpi, Tagliavini, Thorborg Di Stefano and Stignani; Bruno Walter; Charles Kullmann, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_418; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Louis Armstrong; Toscanini; Hootenanny; Olav Trygvason, Greig; Eva Peron; Vanni; Marcoux; Die Brantwahl, Busoni; Romance, Shostakovich; Missa Solemnis; Clarinet Qt., Reger, BBC, 02/25/1939; 06/29/1963; 05/05/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_651; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Love in a Village, Arne; Busoni; Pres. Duvalier (Haiti); Voice of Firestone; Pope Pope VI; Anthony and Cleopatra, Shakespeare, 05/05/1963; 05/12/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_618; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Lucio Silla (Mozart) La Fiamma (Respighi) - Koanga Delius Countess Cathleen (Yeats), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_357; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Lucio Silla, Mozart; La Fiamma, Respighi; Koanga, Delius; Countess Cathleen, Yeats, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_705; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Lucrezia (Respighi) La Bella Dormenta (Respighi); Don Giovanni (Gluck) Symphony #3 (Sammartini); Concerto in F (Vivaldi) Lodoiska (Cherubini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_666; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Lucy Isabelle Marsh - Salvatore Baccaloni - Kirsten Flagstad - Broadway Melody of 1938 (Concluded), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_457; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Luisa Tetrazzini, Pelleas and Melisande, Debussy; Elektra, R. Strauss, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_440; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - M. Garden, Bonanza Bound; Como; Jessonda, Spohr; Joan Sutherland; Perfect Gentleman, Stravinsky, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_566; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - M.. Monroe - D. Shore - Ella F. - J. Sutherland - E. Adams -M. Sahl -Lyndon B. Johnson - Toscanini Rehearsals Traviata (TV) - La Sonnambula; Metropolitan, 03/30/1963; 03/17/1963; 03/26/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_589; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Madam Butterfly, Met, Ninon Vallin; PM East TV Program, 02/03/1962; 02/08/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_382; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Mahalia Jackson; Fred Waring; True to Life; Simon Boccanegra, Verdi; T. Gobbi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_386; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Maj. Gordon Cooper - Leonard Warren - Larry Adler - Dixie (Film) (Bing Crosby), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_635; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Man With a Flower in Mouth 6 Characters in Search of an Author, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_238; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Manhattan Merry Go Round; Music by American Composers; Sing Your Way Home; Sonata in A, Arne; Crazy House, 10/20/1965; bell_brothers_tapes_295; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Manon Metropolitan, 01/16/1943; bell_brothers_tapes_183; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Manon Metropolitan; Lucia Di Lammermoor, NBC Opera; Eugene Onegin, Russian Film, 12/21/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_677; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Manon, Massenet, Metropolitan Opera Broadcast, (Part 1), 12/12/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_174; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Manon, Massenet, Metropolitan Opera Broadcast, (Part 2), (Conclusion); Maurice Chevalieer; Harry Richmand; Paul Robeson; Damsel in Distress, Astaire, 12/12/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_175; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Maria Ivogun; K. Erb; C. Butt; M. Jeritza; P. Ananian; S. Onegin; Hootenanny; Requiem, Bjoerling; Jazz Concert, 05/11/1963; 05/12/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_649; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)